[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The name of the clothing brand Lacoste literally means the cost in French.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the nature of sciences according to Aristotle?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Practical", "Theoretical", "Poetical"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what shape is the Caciocavallo cheese traditionally produced?", "correct_answer": "Tear-drop", "incorrect_answers": ["Ball", "Braid", "Cylinder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the zebra voiced by Chris Rock in the 2008 animated comedy movie Madagascar: Escape 2 Africa?", "correct_answer": "Marty", "incorrect_answers": ["Alex", "Melman", "Maurice"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of climate does North Korea have?", "correct_answer": "Continental", "incorrect_answers": ["Oceanic", "Humid subtropical", "Tropical"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Onega, Khanka and Chudskoye are three of the many lakes in this country.", "correct_answer": "Russia", "incorrect_answers": ["Kazakhstan", "Mongolia", "Ukraine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word refers to the fear of long words?", "correct_answer": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Ornithophobia", "Radiophobia", "Hexakosioihexekontahexaphobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Predator is a type of US Air Force plane. How many people can ride in it ?", "correct_answer": "0", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "1", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these religious movements has many adherents among the people of North Korea?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Korean shamanism", "Cheondoism", "Buddhism"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Mrs. Doubtfires first name in the 1993 comedy movie Mrs. Doubtfire?", "correct_answer": "Euphegenia", "incorrect_answers": ["Wilhelmina", "Gertrude", "Ruth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a group of lions called?", "correct_answer": "Pride", "incorrect_answers": ["Family", "Group", "School"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The effects of red and white wine on your body are comparable.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]